<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nodes>
    <node>
        <name>Bedroom_Morning</name>
        <text>It's morning...</text>
        <transition>
            <input>leave bed</input>
            <output>Left_Bed</output>
            <scene_trans>1</scene_trans>
            <message>WAKE.UP</message>
        </transition>
    </node>
    <node>
        <name>Left_Bed</name>
        <text>Unfortunately, you left your bed</text>
    </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start</name>
    <text> Before we begin this game, we would like to make sure we represent you as closely as possible in this game. So, we’d like to know what you look like.

      What gender are you?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start2</name>
    <text> Alright. How tall are you?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start3</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start3</name>
    <text> I see. Now, what color are your eyes?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start4</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start4</name>
    <text> Oh, stunning! And what color is your hair?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start5</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start5</name>
    <text> A perfect match for your eyes. How long is your hair?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start6</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start6</name>
    <text>Very nice. How would you describe your face shape?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start7</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start7</name>
    <text>Lovely! Any other identifying features?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start8</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start8</name>
    <text>
      Wow. I can see you now.

      I’ll let you start your game now. I hope I captured you perfectly.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>WakeUp</name>
    <text>
      I wake up to my alarm. It’s 6 am. Time to get ready for work. I debate laying in bed for a bit, but I need the money. 
      I get up. I need to get dressed, brush my teeth, and eat breakfast. What do I do first?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>Eat Breakfast</input>
      <output>Breakfast</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>Brush my teeth</input>
      <output>teeth</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>Get dressed</input>
      <output>dressed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Breakfast</name>
    <text>
      I grab a bowl and a box of cereal. Not the healthiest, but its quick. I open the fridge, but there's no milk. 
      I make a mental note to buy more milk as I crunch the dry cereal. Now what should I do now?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>teeth</name>
    <text>
      I grab my toothbrush and squeeze some toothpaste onto it. I brush all the crud off my teeth quickly. 
      After I rinse my mouth out, I check myself in the mirror. I comb my fingers through my hair quickly, before deciding I look fine.
    Now what should I do?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>dressed</name>
    <text>
      I grab some jeans out of the closet and put them on.
      I look at my selection of identical work shirts and sigh. I just grab the first one and put it on.
      Now what should I do?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>ToWork</name>
    <text>
      Time to head out. I grab my keys from the peg near the door. 
      I hop in the car and drive the 10 minutes to work. Traffic is just starting, so luckily, my commute is short.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>AtWork</output>
      <scene_trans>2</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>AtWork</name>
    <text>
      I pull into the small lot and head into the Mart. Paul, the night cashier, is sitting behind the counter reading a magazine. He looks up as the bell rings. 
      He stands, grabs his bag from behind him, and clocks out. “See you tonight”, he says as he leaves. I clock in and make myself comfortable behind the counter.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>5Dollar</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>5Dollar</name>
    <text>
      A man enters, grabs a reheated breakfast sandwich and a mediocre-at-best coffee, and steps up to the counter, waiting for me to scan his items.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>Scan items</input>
      <output>Scanning</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Scanning</name>
    <text>
      I scan the items. As I do so, the man strikes up a conversation. “Did you see the game last night?” 
      “No,” I respond. “Oh,” the man says. He doesn’t say anything else. 
      “That’ll be $3.50”, I say. He hands me a 5 dollar bill. I hand him his change, and he leaves. After him, a few more people enter.
      The morning rush is starting.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>Afternoon</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Afternoon</name>
    <text>
      After a long hour and a half of scanning items and making change, the rush finally ends. 
      I now have a few hours until the lunch rush, and I need to figure out what to do with my time. 
      I could clean the store, restock, or just hang out and read.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>clean the store</input>
      <output>clean</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>restock</input>
      <output>restock</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>read</input>
      <output>read</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>clean</name>
    <text>
      I take out the mop and clean the floor. It's amazing how white the linoleum is when I wash away the dirt. 
      It's also amazing how long it takes me to clean the stores three aisles. I plop down a wet floor sign to ward off any possible lawsuits.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>lunch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>restock</name>
    <text>
      I grab a few boxes from the back and make my way around the store, putting the new packages behind the old ones. I also top off the coffee in the container. 
      Management doesn’t want us to waste coffee. I never drink the coffee here now that I know it's never cleaned.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>lunch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>read</name>
    <text>
      I grab a magazine from the shelf. I don’t really care about the celebrity gossip, but it passes the time.
      And it means I know what everyone is talking about. If I talk to anyone, that is.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>lunch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>lunch</name>
    <text>
      The lunch rush empties out the sandwich case, so I microwave some of the frozen ones in the back before putting them in the heated case.
      Now, I just have to pass the time before the evening rush. I could clean the store, restock, or just hang out and read.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>clean the store</input>
      <output>clean2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>restock</input>
      <output>restock2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>read</input>
      <output>read2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>clean2</name>
      <text>
         I take out the mop and clean the floor. It's amazing how white the linoleum is when I wash away the dirt.
          It's also amazing how long it takes me to clean the stores three aisles. I plop down a wet floor sign to ward off any possible lawsuits.
      </text>
    <transition>
      <output>evening</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>restock2</name>
    <text>
      I grab a few boxes from the back and make my way around the store, putting the new packages behind the old ones. I also top off the coffee in the container.
      Management doesn’t want us to waste coffee. I never drink the coffee here now that I know it's never cleaned.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>evening</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>read2</name>
    <text>
      I grab a magazine from the shelf. I don’t really care about the celebrity gossip, but it passes the time.
      And it means I know what everyone is talking about. If I talk to anyone, that is.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>evening</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>evening</name>
    <text>
      The evening rush is much smaller than the other two, but it is still more than the two people that came in between the rushes. I finish ringing up the last person just as Paul enters. 
      I nod to him and clock out. “You look exhausted,” Paul says, “Go get some sleep”.  As I turn on the car, I check my gas. Not too low. I can go another day at least until refilling it.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>dinner</output>
      <scene_trans>1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>dinner</name>
    <text>
      I put my keys on the peg by the door and head into the kitchen to make myself dinner. 
      Should I make a microwave meal, or make something from scratch?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>microwave meal</input>
      <output>microwave</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>make from scratch</input>
      <output>scratch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>microwave</name>
    <text>
      It may not be healthy, but it’s fast. Once it’s done, I plop myself down on the couch and watch some mindless TV. 
      A good use of my precious time.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>scratch</name>
    <text>
      It takes more effort, but I think it’s worth it. I follow the recipe and make myself a nice, hot meal. 
      I sit down at the table and eat my dinner. It looks like I spent my evening making dinner today.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>ToBed</name>
    <text>
      It’s getting late now, so I need to get ready for bed. 
      I need to brush my teeth, take a shower, and put on my PJ’s.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>brush my teeth</input>
      <output>brush</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>take a shower</input>
      <output>shower</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>put on pjs</input>
      <output>jammies</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>brush</name>
    <text>
      I take my time getting the food residue off my teeth. Shouldn’t let that sit on my teeth all night.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>shower</name>
    <text>
      I wash off the grime of the day. The warm water helps me feel sleepy and get to sleep faster. 
      I look in the foggy mirror as I step out of the shower. Paul was right, I look exhausted.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>jammies</name>
    <text>
      I put on a comfy pair of pants and an old T-shirt. Now I’m ready to sleep.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>beddiebye</name>
    <text>
      I check my alarm for the morning, then get in bed. I need to be well rested for work tomorrow.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
</nodes>