<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<nodes>
  <node>
    <name>Start</name>
    <text> Before we begin this game, we would like to make sure we represent you as closely as possible in this game. So, we’d like to know what you look like. What gender are you?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start2</name>
    <text> Alright. How tall are you?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start3</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start3</name>
    <text> I see. Now, what color are your eyes?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start4</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start4</name>
    <text> Oh, stunning! And what color is your hair?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start5</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start5</name>
    <text> A perfect match for your eyes. How long is your hair?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start6</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start6</name>
    <text>Very nice. How would you describe your face shape?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start7</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start7</name>
    <text>Lovely! Any other identifying features?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>Start8</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Start8</name>
    <text>Wow. I can see you now. I’ll let you start your game now. I hope I captured you perfectly.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>WakeUp</name>
    <text>
      You wake up to your alarm. It’s 6 am. Time to get ready for work. You debate laying in bed for a bit, but you need the money. You get up.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>choices</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>choices</name>
    <text>You need to get dressed, brush your teeth, and eat breakfast. What do you do first?</text>
    <transition>
      <input>Eat Breakfast</input>
      <output>Breakfast</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>Brush your teeth</input>
      <output>teeth</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>Get dressed</input>
      <output>dressed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Breakfast</name>
    <text>You grab a bowl and a box of cereal. Not the healthiest, but its quick. You open the fridge, but there's no milk. You make a mental note to buy more milk as you crunch the dry cereal. Now what should you do now?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>choices</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>teeth</name>
    <text>You grab your toothbrush and squeeze some toothpaste onto it. You brush all the crud off your teeth quickly. After you rinse your mouth out, you check myself in the mirror. you comb your fingers through your hair quickly, before deciding you look fine. Now what should you do?</text>
    <transition>
      <output>choices</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>dressed</name>
    <text>You grab some jeans out of the closet and put them on. You look at your selection of identical work shirts and sigh. You just grab the first one and put it on. Now what should you do?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>choices</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>ToWork</name>
    <text>Time to head out. You grab your keys from the peg near the door. You hop in the car and drive the 10 minutes to work. Traffic is just starting, so luckily, your commute is short.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>AtWork</output>
      <scene_trans>2</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>AtWork</name>
    <text> You pull into the small lot and head into the Mart. Paul, the night cashier, is sitting behind the counter reading a magazine. He looks up as the bell rings. He stands, grabs his bag from behind him, and clocks out. “See you tonight”, he says as he leaves. You clock in and make yourself comfortable behind the counter.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>5Dollar</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>5Dollar</name>
    <text> A man enters, grabs a reheated breakfast sandwich and a mediocre-at-best coffee, and steps up to the counter, waiting for you to scan his items.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>Scan items</input>
      <output>Scanning</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Scanning</name>
    <text>You scan the items. As you do so, the man strikes up a conversation. “Did you see the game last night?”  “No,” you respond. “Oh,” the man says. He doesn’t say anything else. “That’ll be $3.50”, you say. He hands you a 5 dollar bill. You hand him his change, and he leaves. After him, a few more people enter. The morning rush is starting.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>Afternoon</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>Afternoon</name>
    <text>After a long hour and a half of scanning items and making change, the rush finally ends. You now have a few hours until the lunch rush, and you need to figure out what to do with your time. You could clean the store, restock, or just hang out and read.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>clean the store</input>
      <output>clean</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>restock</input>
      <output>restock</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>read</input>
      <output>read</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>clean</name>
    <text>You take out the mop and clean the floor. It's amazing how white the linoleum is when you wash away the dirt. It's also amazing how long it takes you to clean the stores three aisles. You plop down a wet floor sign to ward off any possible lawsuits.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>lunch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>restock</name>
    <text>You grab a few boxes from the back and make your way around the store, putting the new packages behind the old ones. You also top off the coffee in the container. Management doesn’t want to waste coffee. You never drink the coffee here now that you know it's never cleaned.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>lunch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>read</name>
    <text>You grab a magazine from the shelf. You don’t really care about the celebrity gossip, but it passes the time. And it means you know what everyone is talking about. If you talk to anyone, that is.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>lunch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>lunch</name>
    <text>The lunch rush empties out the sandwich case, so you microwave some of the frozen ones in the back before putting them in the heated case. Now, you just have to pass the time before the evening rush. You could clean the store, restock, or just hang out and read.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>clean the store</input>
      <output>clean2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>restock</input>
      <output>restock2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>read</input>
      <output>read2</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>clean2</name>
      <text>You take out the mop and clean the floor. It's amazing how white the linoleum is when you wash away the dirt. It's also amazing how long it takes you to clean the stores three aisles. You plop down a wet floor sign to ward off any possible lawsuits.
      </text>
    <transition>
      <output>evening</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>restock2</name>
    <text>You grab a few boxes from the back and make your way around the store, putting the new packages behind the old ones. You also top off the coffee in the container. Management doesn’t want to waste coffee. You never drink the coffee here now that I know it's never cleaned.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>evening</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>read2</name>
    <text>You grab a magazine from the shelf. You don’t really care about the celebrity gossip, but it passes the time. And it means you know what everyone is talking about. If you talk to anyone, that is.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>evening</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>evening</name>
    <text>The evening rush is much smaller than the other two, but it is still more than the two people that came in between the rushes. You finish ringing up the last person just as Paul enters. You nod to him and clock out. “You look exhausted,” Paul says, “Go get some sleep”.  As you turn on the car, you check my gas. Not too low. You can go another day at least until refilling it.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>dinner</output>
      <scene_trans>1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>dinner</name>
    <text>You put my keys on the peg by the door and head into the kitchen to make yourself dinner. Should you make a microwave meal, or make something from scratch?
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>microwave meal</input>
      <output>microwave</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>make from scratch</input>
      <output>scratch</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>microwave</name>
    <text> It may not be healthy, but it’s fast. Once it’s done, you plop yourself down on the couch and watch some mindless TV. A good use of your precious time.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>scratch</name>
    <text>It takes more effort, but you think it’s worth it. You follow the recipe and make yourself a nice, hot meal. You sit down at the table and eat your dinner. It looks like you spent your evening making dinner today.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>ToBed</name>
    <text>It’s getting late now, so you need to get ready for bed. You need to brush your teeth, take a shower, and put on your PJ’s.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <input>brush your teeth</input>
      <output>brush</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>take a shower</input>
      <output>shower</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
    <transition>
      <input>put on pjs</input>
      <output>jammies</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>brush</name>
    <text>You take your time getting the food residue off your teeth. Shouldn’t let that sit on your teeth all night.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>shower</name>
    <text> You wash off the grime of the day. The warm water helps you feel sleepy and get to sleep faster. You look in the foggy mirror as you step out of the shower. Paul was right, you look exhausted.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>jammies</name>
    <text>You put on a comfy pair of pants and an old T-shirt. Now you're ready to sleep.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>ToBed</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
  <node>
    <name>beddiebye</name>
    <text>You check your alarm for the morning, then get in bed. You need to be well rested for work tomorrow.
    </text>
    <transition>
      <output>WakeUp</output>
      <scene_trans>-1</scene_trans>
    </transition>
  </node>
</nodes>